A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Photographs FA738
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Jobs, 1
  - 506 - Indonesia: Natl. planning, Pop., Agric., 1969 November (Box 31, Folder 495)
    Photographer: Swanson, Richard
  - 507 - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), Nigeria, 1970 April (Box 31, Folder 496)
  - 508 - Wave Hill, Riverdale, New York, 1970 April-May (Box 31, Folder 497)
  - 509 - Indiana University Program Tutoring, 1970 May (Box 32, Folder 498, Box 134, Folder 1950)
    Photographer: Wadelton, Tommy
  - 510 - Navaho Community College, Chinle, Arizona, 1970 May (Box 32, Folder 499)
  - 511 - Rough Rock Demonstration School, Arizona, 1970 May (Box 32, Box 134, Folder 1951)
    Photographer: Daniels, Gene. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 512 - Philadelphia Tutorial Project, 1970 May (Box 32, Folder 500)
    Photographer: Arenholz, Eileen
  - 513 - Vera Institute Summons Project, 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 501)
    Photographer: Harris, Jack
  - 514 - Stanford University - Undergraduate Ecology, 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 502)
  - 515 - Colorado College (Venture Fund), 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 503)
  - 516 - Newark Community Center of the Arts, 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 504)
  - 517 - University of Washington Pop Barnes/Wilson, 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 505)
    Photographer: Wilson, Doug
  - 518 - Harvard Community Health Plan, 1970 October (Box 32, Folder 506)
  - 519 - Ghana University of, and G.I.M.P.A., 1970 November (Box 32, Folder 507)
    Photographer: Redl, Harry
  - 520 - Venezuela Management Training, Caracas, 1970 November (Box 32, Folder 508)
    Photographer: Pelham, Lynn
  - 521 - Tarcuato Di Tella Institute, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1971 May (Box 32, Folder 509)
  - 522 - International Center of Tropical Agriculture, CIAT, Colombia (Box 32, Folder 510. 511)
  - 523 - Latin America and the Caribbean program (LAC) - University of the Valley Head-Start Program, 1971 May (Box 33, Folder 512)
  - 524 - College of Mexico, 1971 May (Box 33, Folder 513)
    Mexico
  - 525 - Howard University, 1971 September (Box 33, Folder 514)
    Photographer: Caselloe, Maggi
  - 526 - Berkeley (California) Unified School District, 1971 October (Box 33, Folder 515)
  - 527 - East Central Committee for Opportunity, 1971 November (Box 33, Folder 516)
  - 528 - Center for Understanding Media (Box 33, Folder 517)
    Photographer: Watteston, Ellie
  - 529 - The Woodlawn Organization (CDC), 1972 October (Box 33, Folder 518)
    Photographer: Rozumalski, Ted
  - 530 - Catalyst, 1972 November 8 (Box 33, Folder 519)
    Photographer: Harris, Kay
  - 531 - VERA and UPACA, 1972 November (Box 33, Folder 520)
    Photographer: Higgins, Chester
  - 532 - Advanced Study and Doctoral Fellowships, 1972 September (Box 33, Folder 521)
  - 533 - Foundation Luncheon Group, 1973 February (Box 33, Folder 522)
    Photographer: Pickens, M. No prints in file, see negatives.
  - 534 - Mokan Minority Contractors Association - KC (Box 33, Folder 523)
    Photographer: Hanna, Rod
  - 535 - Ford Foundation Board of Directors Officers Meeting, 1972 December (Box 34, Folder 524)
    Photographer: Marmaras, John
  - 536 - Leadership Development Program, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 525)
  - 537 - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 526)
    Photographer: Dukes, Tyrone
  - 538 - Leadership Development Program: Linda Bullock (Box 34, Folder 527)
  - 539 - Pop University of Kansas, Dr. Gilbert Greenwald (Box 34, Folder 528)
  - 540 - Community Development Corporation (UPACA), 1973 March 29 (Box 34, Folder 529)
  - 541 - ECCO Community Development Corporation, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 530)
  - 542 - Zion Community Development Corp., 1973 March (Box 34, Folder 531)
  - 543 - SEASHA: Community Development Corporation, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 532)
  - 545 - National Affairs program - Social Development: Community Development Fund, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 534)
  - 546 - Neighborhood Housing Services - DC, 1973 September (Box 34, Folder 535)
    Photographer: Molony, Mike
  - 547 - Spanish Speaking Unity Council - Oakland, 1973 October (Box 35, Folder 536)
    Photographer: Springman, Christopher
  - 548 - Harvard University: Prof. Guttentag: Massachussetts (Box 35, Folder 537)
  - 549 - Mountain View Center: Boulder, CO., 1973 March (Box 35, Folder 538)
  - 550 - The Worship Center: NY, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 539)
    Photographer: Adelman, Bob
  - 551 - Women's Law Fund: Cleveland, OH, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 540)
  - 552 - Feminist Press: New York, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 541)
  - 544 - MACE (Mississippi Action for Community Education): Community Development Corporation, 1973 April (Box 34, Folder 533)
  - 553 - Union Women, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 542)
  - 554 - Day Care Centers: New York, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 543)
  - 555 - Dr. Lundberg: Single Parent Meeting, 1974 March (Box 35, Folder 544)
  - 556 - Shaw University: Raleigh, NC, 1974 August (Box 35, Folder 545)
    Photographer: Fletcher, Bob
  - 557 - Trans-Bay Builders: Oakland, CA, 1974 August (Box 35, Folder 546)
  - 558 - Hubbard Company: Emeryville, CA, 1974 August (Box 35, Folder 547)
  - 559 - San Francisco Gold Co., 1974 August (Box 35, Folder 548)
  - 560 - Southern Consumers Co-Op, 1974 August (Box 35, Folder 549)
  - 561 - Bedford-Stuyvesant Commercial Center: Brooklyn, NY, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 550)
  - 563 - Erie County Department of Health, 1974 September (Box 35, Folder 551, Box 134, Folder 1952)
    Photographer: Karol, John
  - 567 - Ford Foundation Officers Meeting, 1978 October (Box 35, Folder 552)
  - 568 - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979 March (Box 35, Folder 553)
    Photographer: Gladstone, Gary
  - 569 - Sundial Compass Presented to M. Bundy, 1979 May (Box 35, Folder 554)
    Photographer: Choplin, Leo
  - 570 - Franklin Thomas Appointment as Ford Foundation President Announcement, 1979 January (Box 35, Folder 555)
  - 571 - MACE (Mississippi Action for Community Education) photography exhibit, 1979 September (Box 36, Folder 556, Box 145)
    Photographer: Smith, Bud. Includes 8x10 prints, negatives, 35mm slides, exhibition text panels, copy negatives of text panels, and copy negatives of images. Oversize materials housed in Box 145.
  - 572 - University of Pennsylvania Museum Lab Ban Chiang, 1979 September (Box 36, Folder 557)
  - 573 - Bangladesh: Diarrheal Institute, 1980 January (Box 36, Folder 558)
    Photographer: Witlin, Ray
    Bangladesh
  - 574 - Indonesia: Ecology Institute, 1980 February (Box 36, Folder 559)
  - 575 - Photos of Franklin Thomas, 1981 March (Box 36, Folder 560)
    Photographer: Silk, Georgiana
  - 576 - Photos of William Carmichael and Susan Beresford, 1981 March (Box 36, Folder 561)
  - 577 - Humanities Awards Lunch, 1981 December (Box 36, Folder 562)
  - 578 - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 36, Folder 563)
  - 579 - Susan Berresford and William Carmichael at Work (Box 36, Folder 564)
  - 580 - National Irrigation Administration, 1982 September (Box 36, Folder 565)
    Photographer: Viesti, Joe
  - 581 - Indonesian Tea Pickers Etc., 1982 September (Box 36, Folder 566)
  - 582 - Children's Storefront, 1983 January (Box 36, Folder 567)
    Photographer: Stanton, Brian
  - 583 - Preservation of Folk Performing Arts, 1982 November (Box 37, Folder 568)
  - 584 - Self Employed Women's Association (SEWA), 1982 November (Box 37, Folder 569)
  - 585 - Pride Gardens, 1983 February (Box 37, Folder 570)
  - 586 - Savannah Landmark Rehabilitation Project, 1983 February (Box 37, Folder 571)
  - 587 - Chicanos Por La Causa, 1983 February (Box 37, Folder 572)
  - 588 - Jersey City Y, 1983 February (Box 37, Folder 573)
  - 589 - Boricua College, 1983 February (Box 37, Folder 574)
  - 590 - Nepal Women's Organization, 1983 May (Box 37, Folder 575)
    Photographer: Maines, Steve
  - 591 - Chiang Mai University: Multiple Croppings, 1983 May (Box 38, Folder 576)
    Thailand
  - 592 - Grameen Bank, Bangladesh, 1983 February (Box 38, Folder 577)
  - 593 - Northwestern University: Health Services, 1983 October (Box 38, Folder 578)
  - 594 - Corp. for Public/Private Ventures, 1983 October (Box 38, Folder 579)
  - 595 - Center for Rural Affairs - Nebraska, 1983 October (Box 38, Folder 580)
  - 596 - High School Recognition Program: Bronx, New York, 1983 June (Box 38, Folder 581)
    Photographer: Lewis, Connie
  - 596A - Self Center for Teenage Pregnancy, 1983 June (Box 38, Folder 582)
    Photographer: Brown, V.E.
  - 597 - People's Firehouse: Community Development, 1983 March (Box 38, Folder 583)
    Photographer: Moore, Susan
  - 598 - Pune Irrigation Project, 1983 February (Box 38, Folder 584)
  - 599 - Corp for Public/Private Ventures, 1983 December (Box 38, Folder 585)
  - 600 - Designwrights Collaboratives, 1983 December (Box 38, Folder 586)
  - 601 - Center for Development Of Non-Formal Education, 1983 December (Box 38, Folder 587)
  - 602 - Amistad Research Center: New Orleans, 1983 December (Box 38, Folder 588)
  - 603 - Barrio Education Project: San Antonio (File Missing), 1983 December (Box 39, Folder 589)
    Photographer: Viesti, Joe. No prints or negatives available. File is missing.
  - 604 - MDC: Opportuns. Industrialization Center, 1983 December (Box 39, Folder 590)
  - 605 - Redlands Christian Migrant Association (RCMA), 1983 December (Box 39, Folder 591)
  - 606 - Save the Children Federation, 1983 November (Box 39, Folder 592)
    Photographer: Lyons, Martin
  - 607 - Water Research Center: West Bank, 1983 November (Box 39, Folder 593)
  - 608 - Mattin Cooperative: West Bank, 1983 November (Box 39, Folder 594)
  - 609 - Mugattam Zabaleen Association, Cairo, 1983 November (Box 39, Folder 595)
  - 610 - Vocational Youth Center, Dakar, 1983 December (Box 39, Folder 596)
    Photographer: Chiasson, John
    Senegal
  - 611 - Historical Museum of Senegal (File Missing), 1983 December (Box 39, Folder 597)
    Photographer: Chiasson, John. No prints or negatives available. File is missing.
  - 612 - Miami Dade Community College, 1984 May (Box 39, Folder 598)
    Photographer: Vergara, Camillo
  - 613 - Tacolcy CDC: Otis Pitts and Shopping Center, 1984 May (Box 39, Folder 599)
  - 614 - High School Improvement: Memphis, Tennessee, 1984 January (Box 39, Folder 600)
    Photographer: Darnell, Dave
  - 615 - Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1984 September (Box 39, Folder 601)
  - 616 - Mountain Association for Community Economic Development (MACED), 1984 September (Box 39, Folder 602)
  - 617 - Coal Employment Project: Cumberland, 1984 September (Box 39, Folder 603)
  - 618 - Virginia Water Project, 1984 September (Box 40, Folder 604)
  - 619 - YWCA of Kenya: Income Generation, 1984 October (Box 40, Folder 605)
  - 620 - Rural Industrial Development Trust, 1984 October (Box 40, Folder 606)
  - 621 - Partnership for Productivity, 1984 October (Box 40, Folder 607)
  - 622 - Cultural Preservation: Indonesia: Puppets, Manuscripts, Dance: Bedoyo, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 608)
    Photographer: Berry, Paul. Includes captions and B&W contact (proof) sheets.
  - 622 - Cultural Preservation: Indonesia: Puppets, Manuscripts, Dance: Bedoyo, 1983 (Box 69)
    Photographer: Berry, Paul. Includes 4x6 and 5x7 color prints.
  - 623a - Hyderabad Urban Development and Authority, 1984 April (Box 40, Folder 609)
    Photographer: Satyan, T.S.
  - 623b - Mexican Farmwokers - Letter, 1985 December (Box 40, Folder 610)
    Photographer: Gestner, John
  - 624 - Dandora Catholic Church project, Nairobi, Kenya: Housing and income generation for female-headed households, 1985 August (Box 40, Folder 611)
    Photographer: Hollyman, Stephanie
  - 625 - Undugu Society, Nairobi Carpentry: Establishment of a technical upgrading center for upgrading skills in carpentry, 1985 August (Box 40, Folder 612)
  - 626 - Land and Water Management in Indonesia: Irrigation canal systems in Bali - farming and village life, 1985 September (Box 40, Folder 613)
  - 627 - Agroecosystems in Java (Agroecosystems Network, KEPA): Brawijaya University Research C3nter, Malang conducting Surveys, in villages as well as on farms, 1985 September (Box 66, Folder 1016)
  - 628 - Indonesian Academy for the Performing Arts, Bali: Documentation and study of traditional Balinese music, dance, and dance-drama, 1985 September (Box 66, Folder 1017)
  - 629 - Indonesia Ministry of forestry: The interaction of forest lands with adjacent communities; farming, harvesting, women with firewood, and inspection of national forests, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1018)
  - 630 - Dandora Project, Nairobi, Kenya: Housing finance project to make small loans to poorer residents to enable them to build, 1985 August (Box 67, Folder 1019)
  - 631 - Jebel Marra Development Project, Zlinqei, Sudan: Agro-forestry to improve harvests and horticulture practices, 1985 August (Box 67, Folder 1020)
  - 632 - Children's Hospital, Khartoum: Children being treated while mothers stay to care for them and get instruction on hygiene, nutrition, etc., 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1021)
  - 633 - El Gazira Irrigation Scheme, Wad Medani: University of El Gazira students working farm; irrigation system photos, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1022)
  - 634 - Euro-Action ACORD, Port Sudan: Income generating projects for refugees from Tigray and Eritrea, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1023)
  - 635 - Institute of Environment Studies, University of Khartoum: Students using maps, library, computer, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1024)
  - 636 - National Museum, Khartoum: Art Preservation and restoration, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1025)
  - 637 - Undugu Society, Nairobi: Income generation, men learning auto repair and furniture building, 1985 September (Box 67, Folder 1026)
  - 638 - GLIE Community Youth Program, Bronx NY: Herb nursery supplying supermarkets and restaurants, 1986 May (Box 67, Folder 1027)
    Photographer: Richard Hertzberg
  - 639 - Better Babies, Washington DC, 1986 May (Box 67, Folder 1028)
    Photographer: Joe Viesti
  - 640 - Urban Affairs Corp. Houston, Texas, 1986 May (Box 67, Folder 1029)
  - 641 - Africa News Service, 1986 May (Box 67, Folder 1030)
  - 642 - District of Columbia: Public Schools (Washington DC), 1986 May (Box 67, Folder 1031)
  - 643 - Mainstreaming Seminar at Columbia University, 1986 May (Box 68, Folder 1032)
    Photographer: Zeva Oelbaum
  - 644 - Mendenhall Ministries, 1986 December (Box 68, Folder 1033)
  - 645 - Khon Kaen University: Thailand, 1986 May (Box 68, Folder 1034)
    Photographer: Finck, John
  - 646 - Rensselaerville Institute, Water Project in New York, 1986 May (Box 41, Folder 614)
    Photographer: Kniskern, Paul
  - 647 - Workshop on International Security, aram Central and Disarmament, Univ. Md. (Chinese Students), 1986 August (Box 41, Folder 615)
    Photographer: Berg, Lisa
  - 648 - Public/Private Ventures Summer Training and Education Program, Fresno, CA, 1986 July (Box 41, Folder 616)
    Photographer: Mertz, Fred
  - 649 - Center for Southeast Asian Refugee Resettlement (San Francisco), 1986 July (Box 41, Folder 617)
  - 650 - Aspira of America, San Franciso: Hispanic Leadership Opportunity Program, 1986 July (Box 41, Folder 618)
  - 651 - Womens Research and Education Institute Conference, 1986 May (Box 41, Folder 619)
    Photographer: Garrett, Kenneth
  - 652 - Florence Howe, Director, Feminist Press, 1986 July (Box 41, Folder 620)
  - 653 - Oakland Directions, Inc.: Pittsburgh, PA, 1986 September (Box 41, Folder 621)
    Photographer: Kroessler, Jeffrey
  - 654 - Khon Kaen University Thailand: Water Project, 1986 October (Box 41, Folder 622)
  - 655 - Khon Kaen University: Bangkok, Thailand, 1986 October (Box 41, Folder 623)
  - 656 - Indochinese Refugees, Vietnamese Refugee Center, 1987 February (Box 41, Folder 624)
    Vietnam
  - 657 - Port City: Lamu, Kenya, 1987 February (Box 41, Folder 625)
    Photographer: Borst, Barbara
  - 658 - Community Foundation Awards, 1987 January (Box 41, Folder 626)
  - 659 - Indochinese Psychiatry Clinic: Cambodian Refugees, 1987 February (Box 41, Folder 627)
    Photographer: Stewart, Martha
    Cambodia
  - 660 - Spofford Juvenile Detention Center (No Photos), 1987 February (Box 41, Folder 628)
    Photographer: Halverson, Karen
  - 661 - Brian Urquhart: June 1987 'Ford Foundation Letter', 1987 February (Box 41, Folder 629)
  - 662 - Plan Sierra: June1987 'Ford Foundation Letter', 1987 June (Box 42, Folder 630)
  - 663 - Youth Oregon, 1987 June (Box 42, Folder 631)
  - 664 - Youth Project, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1987 June (Box 42, Folder 632)
  - 665 - South Shore Bank projects, Chicago, Illinois, 1987 May (Box 42, Folder 633)
  - 666 - International Refugee Center, 1987 May (Box 42, Folder 634)
  - 667 - Cambridge Design Lab: The Lab for Making Things, 1987 June (Box 42, Folder 635)
  - 668 - Portable Practical Educational Prep. Douglas, AZ, 1987 June (Box 42, Folder 636)
  - 669 - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1987 February (Box 42, Folder 637)
    Photographer: Bloom, Richard
  - 699 - Padjadjaran University: Irrigation, South Sumatra, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 638)
    Photographer: Franken, Owen
  - 700 - Sriwijaya University, West Java: Diarrheal Care, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 639)
  - 701 - Andean Commission of Jurist, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 640)
    Photographer: Antmann, Fran
    Peru
  - 702 - Cipca Piura, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 641)
  - 703 - Peruvian Center for International Studies (CEPEI) (No photos), 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 642)
  - 704 - Peru: Mujer, Lima, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 643)
  - 705 - University of Padjadjaran, West Java, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 644)
  - 706 - International Irrigation Management Institute, West Java, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 645)
  - 707 - Black Scholars at the Ford Foundation, 1987 September (Box 43, Folder 646)
  - 708 - Committee for Legal Educational Exchange with China (CLEEC), 1987 September (Box 43, Folder 647)
    Photographer: Oelbaum, Zeva
  - 709 - Committee for Economic Education and Research with China, 1987 September (Box 43, Folder 648)
  - 710 - American University of Cairo, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 649)
  - 711 - University of Minia, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 650)
  - 712 - Old City, Small Business, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 651)
  - 713 - Environmental Quality International, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 652)
  - 714 - Princeton University: Seminar Faculty for Freshman Seminars, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 653)
  - 715 - University of Wisconsin, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 654)
    Photographer: Garfinkel, Irwin
  - 716 - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Ceremony, 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 655)
  - 717 - Fund for Peace: National Security Archives: Scott Armstrong, 1988 January (Box 43, Folder 656)
    Photographer: Chernush, Kay
  - 718 - University of the Philippines, 1988 January (Box 43, Folder 657)
    Photographer: Garcia, Alberto/ Picture Group
  - 719 - Urban Math Collaboratives: Math Teachers at the San Francisco Exploratorium, 1986 December (Box 43, Folder 658)
    Photographer: Ressmeyer, Roger
  - 720 - LaGuardia Community College, Middle College, NYC, 1988 January (Box 43, Folder 659)
  - 721 - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. (MDRC), 1987 December (Box 43, Folder 660)
  - 722 - Conference on Hispanic Issues and Foundation Community, 1987 February (Box 43, Folder 661)
    Photographer: Halvenson, Karen
  - 723 - Innovations in State and Local Government: 1987 Award Winners, 1987 September (Box 43, Folder 662)
  - 724 - Designwrights, Santa Fe, NM: Wealth of Water, 1988 February (Box 43, Folder 663)
    Photographer: Morris, Scott
  - 725 - Drew Economic Development Corp., Los Angeles, 1988 April (Box 44, Folder 664)
  - 726 - Government of Indonesia: State Forestry Program, Kalinusu, Indonesia, 1987 October (Box 44, Folder 665)
    Photographer: Pincus, Jonathan
  - 727 - Center for Immigrants Rights, New York, 1987 November (Box 44, Folder 666)
  - 729 - Institute for East-West Security Studies, 1986 May (Box 44, Folder 667)
  - 730 - New York Mission Society (Box 44, Folder 668)
    Photographer: Reiman, Cindy
  - 731 - Columbia University (Committee for Legal Exchanges with China) (Box 44, Folder 669)
  - 732 - Grameen Bank (Box 44, Folder 670)
    Photographer: Goldberg, Beryl
  - 733 - Princeton University, 1987 April (Box 44, Folder 671)
  - 734 - Frank Furstenberg, 1987 April (Box 44, Folder 672)
  - 735 - National Dairy Development Bank, India, 1987 April (Box 44, Folder 673)
    Photographer: Rose, Kalima
  - 736 - University of Chiang Mai, Thailand: Social Foresting and Irrigation, 1988 April (Box 44, Folder 674)
    Photographer: Stone, Wendy
  - 737 - Franklin Chen and Henry Mosely, 1988 June (Box 44, Folder 675)
  - 738 - Low-Income Housing Fund: Daniel Leibsohn, 1988 August (Box 44, Folder 676)
    Photographer: Mertz, Fred/ Beckerman, Larry
  - 739 - Bridge, I. Donald Terner (San Francisco), 1988 August (Box 44, Folder 677, Box 134, Folder 1953)
  - 740 - University of Zimbabwe, 1988 August (Box 44, Folder 678)
    Zimbabwe
  - 741 - Robert Curvin, Director of Urban Poverty program, 1988 August (Box 44, Folder 679)
  - 742 - Self-Employed Women's Association, 1988 August (Box 44, Folder 680)
    Photographer: Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc.
  - 743 - Child Survival (India), 1987 (Box 44, Folder 681)
    Photographer: Silver Studio and Art Gallery
  - 744 - Chicanos Por La Causa, 1988 September (Box 44, Folder 682)
    Photographer: Moore, Terrance
  - 745 - Judith Gueron, MDRC, 1988 November (Box 44, Folder 683)
  - 746 - Project for the Preservation of Traditional Andean Music, 1988 August (Box 45, Folder 684)
  - 747 - Bangladesh Women's Health Coalition: Proshika, BRAC, Grameen Bank, 1988 November (Box 45, Folder 685)
    Photographer: Lurie, Theodora
  - 748 - Farag M. Elkamel Center for Development Communication, 1988 October (Box 45, Folder 686)
    Photographer: Miller, J.T.
  - 749 - Rubber Trappers of the Amazon, 1987 October (Box 45, Folder 687)
    Photographer: May, Peter
  - 750 - Brian Urquhart: 1988 Nobel Peace Prize Awards Ceremony, 1989 February (Box 45, Folder 688)
    Photographer: Knive, Erik; Grant, M.; Isaac, J.
  - 751 - Bilateral Commission on the Future of U.S. Mexico Relations, 1989 February (Box 45, Folder 689)
  - 752 - Philadelphia Youth Services Corp. Public/Private Ventures, 1989 February (Box 45, Folder 690)
  - 753 - Profile: Catherine Kelleher, 1989 February (Box 45, Folder 691)
  - 754 - Corrective Capitalism Photos, 1987 July (Box 45, Folder 692, 693, 694)
    Photographer: Sherbill, Shepard
  - 755 - Dandora Project - Kenya, 1987 August (Box 46, Folder 695)
  - 756 - Hispanic Leadership Opportunities Program, 1989 April (Box 46, Folder 696)
    Photographer: Halebian, Carol/ Gamma Liaison
  - 757 - University of Pennsylvania (Social Science Initiative for Undergraduates), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 697)
  - 758 - University of Washington (Northwest Regional Consortium for SE Studies), 1989 April (Box 46, Folder 698)
    Photographer: Donnelly, Nancy
  - 759 - University of Chicago (Undergraduate social science teaching 88 AR), 1989 February (Box 46, Folder 699)
    Photographer: Joel, David
  - 760 - International Council of Archives (Medal of Honor to Ford Foundation)/Frank Thomas, 1989 May (Box 46, Folder 700)
    Photographer: Gamma Liaison
  - 761 - Opening to the Outside World, 1989 August (Box 46, Folder 701)
    China
  - 762a - Southern Development Bancorporation, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 702)
  - 762b - Good Faith Fund, Pine Bluff, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 703)
    Photographer: Kilgore, Andrew
  - 762c - North Carolina Center for Community Self-Help, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 704)
  - 763a - SEEDCO, 1989 November (Box 46, Folder 705)